http://www.lodge320.co.uk/privacy-policy

HomeAbout usNewsMeetingsSocial ClubSocial ClubPast MastersOffice BearersGalleryContact UsMoreHomeAbout usNewsMeetingsSocial ClubSocial ClubPast MastersOffice BearersGalleryContact UsHomeAbout usNewsMeetingsSocial ClubPast MastersOffice BearersGalleryContact UsLodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan
No.320Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan
No.320Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan
No.320Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan
No.320
The Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website is produced and made available in good faith.Neither the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 nor any of it's Trustees, Office Bearers or members give or make any representations or warranties of any kind, whether express, actual or implied, in relation to all or any part of the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website or any contents thereof or any website or websites to which the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 is linked.
All warranties and representations of every kind and howsoever arising are hereby absolutely and expressly excluded to the fullest extent permitted by law. Liability for material reproduced on the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website remains with the author(s) and/or originator(s) of the material concerned and not the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320.The content of the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website does not constitute the dispensation or giving of any kind of advice, recommendations or guidance by or on behalf of the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 and must not be relied upon in making, or refraining from making, any decision.
There is no guarantee that the website will be free from infection whether by viruses or from any other cause or source which may be harmful or destructive. All parties use the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website entirely at their own risk and without recourse to the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320, it's Office Bearers, Trustees and members or any of them.
To the fullest extent permitted by law, the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 and, separately, it's Office Bearers, Trustees and members, all jointly and severally hereby disclaim all liability (howsoever arising) in connection with any loss or damage, arising out of or in connection with any use of, or inability to use, all or any part of the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website or any site to which the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website is linked or any action taken (or not taken) as a result of access to the use of any of these.
The Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 intends that the information published on the website is up to date and accurate. However, the information on the website does not constitute legal or professional advice, guidance or recommendation and the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320, it's Office Bearers, Trustees and members and each of them, will not accept any liability for actions arising from it's use nor will they be held responsible for the contents of any website or other source referenced by any external site.
Links to External WebsitesThe Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 has included, or may include, links to third party internet websites controlled and maintained by others. When accessing these sites the user leaves the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website.
These links are included solely for the convenience of users and their presence does not constitute any endorsement by the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 of the websites linked or referred to nor does the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 have any control over, or responsibility for, the content of any such website.
Privacy policyThe Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 recognises the importance of protecting the privacy of visitors to the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website.Any personal data collected through the website will be regarded and treated as confidential and in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998.
Names and email addresses are collected for the sole purpose of answering individual enquiries forwarded to the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 via the contact and/or guestbook form(s) on the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website. Under no circumstances will these details be intentionally used for any purpose.
CopyrightThe information contained on this website is the Copyright © property of Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 (unless otherwise stated) and is protected by international copyright laws.
The Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website is provided for personal, private and non-commercial use only.
No user or recipient has any right to modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derived works from, transfer, exchange or sell any information, material, software, images, graphics or source code obtained from the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website.No part of the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website may be reproduced in any form whether electronic or otherwise (other than temporarily in the course of using the website) without the express prior written consent of the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320.
Editorial ControlLodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 can exercise editorial control only over material commissioned and/or produced by it.The Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 cannot, under any circumstances change, add to, or subtract from, any material previously produced by others, that is prior to reproduction by the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320.Errors and omissions in such previously reproduced material are the responsibility of the authors or commissioning body and not the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320. Errors and omissions in material reproduced on the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website which do not occur in the original material should be brought to the attention of the Webmaster. If correction is required, the full text of the original material, author, source, date and place(s) of primary publication must be submitted to the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 which will then make the appropriate adjustments and corrections having regard to the submissions.
CookiesA cookie is a small data file that certain Websites write to a hard drive when a user visits that Website.The only personal information a cookie can contain is information a user personally supplies. A cookie cannot read data from a user's hard disk or read cookie files created by other Websites.
Cookies, however, enhance a Website's performance in a number of ways including providing a secure way for to identity verification during a visit to a Website and personalising the user's experience with the Lodge Website while making it more convenient for the user.The Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website uses cookie technology to track or record information about visitors to the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website. These cookies are 'session specific', and only in the form of a unique visitor indentification code which is generated at the time the user visits the Website. They are not used to record personal information or to associate personal information with the use of the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 services.
Privacy and security are not compromised if and when the user accepts a cookie from the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website.Users can refuse cookies by turning them off on their web browsers. This will not affect the general use of the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website.
The use of cookies however, is required if the user wishes to log into the Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320 website as a member.
How To Disable CookiesTo turn off cookies in your browser, use the link below for your respective browser:· Cookies in Internet Explorer· Cookies in Firefox· Cookies in Chrome· Cookies in Safari
Copyright © 2019  Lodge St John Royal Arch Saltcoats & Ardrossan No.320  - All Rights Reserved.HomeAbout usNewsMeetingsSocial ClubPast MastersOffice BearersGalleryContact UsLinksPrivacy Policy
